There are times when excitement
works better to purify Hue...
時に興奮状態が　色相の浄化に役立つ場合がある
Even more than trying
to always maintain calm.
常に　穏やかでいようとするよりも
Wh-Who's there?
だ…　誰
No!
嫌ーっ
Sorry. I really needed
an eye from an Inspector.
すまない　僕にはどうしても監視官の目が必要だったんだ
Crime Coefficient is 129.
She is a target for enforcement action.
「犯罪係数　１２９」
「執行対象です」
No...! No!
嫌…　嫌ーっ
Your fear will end soon, Mizue Shisui.
恐怖は今だけだ　酒々井水絵
I'll make you clear to make up
for taking your eye.
君をクリアにしてみせる
君の目のおわびに
I understand very well
how you are suffering.
君の苦しみは　よく分かる
Your worries about your Hue worsening
every time a crime occurs...
事件が起こるたび　自分の色相が悪化する不安
いつ　牙をむくか分からない　執行官への恐れ
Your fears towards Enforcers,
who may turn on you at any time...
What holds you back
is you, yourself.
君を縛り付けているのは　君自身だ
You have the strength
to accept any circumstances.
君はどんな境遇も受け入れてしまう　強さを持っている
But, that's exactly why
you've been suffering.
でも　だからこそ　苦しんできた
Now I'm going to release you
from yourself... from Sibyl.
今　君を　君自身から…　シビュラから解放する
Remember...
思い出すんだ
忘れてしまった　本当の自分を
...the true you from long ago...
...the one you've come to forget.
「対象の脅威判定が更新されました」
Target's Threat Judgment
has been updated.
Crime Coefficient is 85.
「犯罪係数　８５」
Not a target for enforcement action.
「執行対象ではありません」
Who are you?
あなたは？
My name is Kirito Kamui.
僕の名は　鹿矛囲桐斗
I want to make you
and this world clear...
君と　この世界をクリアにしたい
...so clear that
they're completely invisible.
限りなく透明に
奪われ続けるなら
If I keep having things taken away from me, I'm gonna lose my mind
Ubaware tsuzukeru nara mou kurutte shimau yo
奪われ続けるなら
もう狂ってしまうよ
This endless "end" will make me stop breathing
Owari no nai "owari" ni boku wa iki wo shinaku natte
終わりの無い「終わり」に僕は息をしなくなって
Enigmatic Feeling
Enigmatic feeling
Why do they have to take things away from me? I'm about to fall apart
Ubawanakya ikenai no? Mou hodokete shimau yo
奪わなきゃいけないの
もうほどけてしまうよ
世界が溶け出して
The world began to melt
Sekai ga tokedashite
もうほどけてしまうよ
世界が溶け出して
神様が降りて来て
God descended to confront and ask me
Kami-sama ga orite kite boku ni tsukitsuketa
神様が降りて来て
僕に突きつけた
"Who are you?"
Who are you?
I freed myself by walking in the divide of this world broken into two
Futatsu ni wakareta sekai ni sotte jibun wo hanatta
２つに分かれた世界に沿って
自分を放った
Is there only one God in such a fine borderline?
Kamihitoe darou kamihitoe darou kyoukaisen kami wa hitori na no?
紙一重だろう　紙一重だろう
境界線　神は１人なの
I'm gonna lose my mind, I'm gonna lose my mind...
Okashiku natte okashiku natte
おかしくなって おかしくなって
Suddenly I'll find myself taking you away
Fui ni kimi wo ubatte shimau no darou
ふいに君を奪ってしまうのだろう
Crazy! Crazy!
Crazy Crazy　完全浮遊体
I'm completely adrift
Kanzen fuyuutai
Crazy Crazy　完全浮遊体
Because my heart can't focus
Pinto no awanai kokoro ni
ピントの合わない心に
Shake me! Shake me!
Shake me Shake me　完全浮遊体
I'm completely adrift
Kanzen fuyuutai
Shake me Shake me　完全浮遊体
I can't even look into the mirror
Kagami sae mo nozokenai
鏡さえも覗けない
#3: The Devil's Proof
In any case,
this place is quite a mess.
しかし　ずいぶん　荒らされているな
Excuse me for not being
more organized.
悪かったですね　片付け　下手で
Inspector Tsunemori, it may not be too late.
Therapy may be able to help you.
先輩　今ならまだ　セラピーで解消できるかもしれません
You're trying to say that I was the one
who wrote this, Ms. Shimotsuki?
これを書いたのが私だって言いたいんだね　霜月さんは
The scans for this area didn't
detect anyone suspicious,
周辺のスキャンデータに　不審な人物はなし
which means no one
entered your apartment.
ということは　誰も侵入していないことになる
You think so too, Mr. Ginoza?
宜野座さんもそう思いますか
私が正気を失って　こんな文字を書いたと
That I lost my mind
and wrote this?
だったら　ドミネーターを向けて　私の色相を調べてみてください
Then point your Dominator at me
and check my Hue.
そんなことは…
That's...
What're you doing?
何してるの　侵入者はいないって聞こえなかった？
Didn't you just hear that
no one had entered here?
There's no way someone
could have broken in.
侵入者など　いるはずがない
But, there's also no reason to think
that the Inspector lost her mind.
だが　同時に　監視官が正気を失ったとも考えられない
現状　起こり得ないことが　２つ重なっている
So as things stand, we're faced
with two impossible scenarios.
But one of them
definitely happened.
しかし　必ず　どちらかが　起こった
If the chances of each happening
is equally probable...
２つの可能性が等価なら
Enforcers should trust
the Inspector.
執行官は監視官を信じるべきだ
Mr. Togane...
東金さん…
Based on the rules, your family
should be moved to a safe location
規律に従い　先輩のご家族は安全な場所で
and put under the protection
of guard Drones...
警護ドローンの保護下に置かれるはずです
...although I have my doubts
that there is any necessity for that.
その必要性に関して　私は疑問に感じますが
I guess my parents will be moved
to a nearby MWPSB facility...
両親は最寄りの公安直下施設に　移住ってところかな
...though it might be difficult
for my grandma.
おばあちゃんは　ちょっと　難しいけど
Difficult?
難しい？
動けないんだ　おばあちゃん
She can't move.
I see.
そうですか
Go right at the next fork.
次の分岐を右に入って
The MWPSB is straight ahead.
公安局は　ここを真っすぐですよ
There's a stop
I want to make first.
寄りたい所があるの
You could've just left me here
and gone back.
先に戻ってくれて　よかったのに
You're an Inspector.
What business do you have going to an isolation facility?
監視官が隔離施設に　何の用ですか
I have a duty
to learn the answer.
私には　それを知る義務があります
What a surprise.
I didn't expect to see you.
これは　珍しいお客さんだ
Jouji Saiga?!
雑賀譲二
You know him?
知ってるの？
Yeah... I saw his file.
そりゃあ　資料で見ましたから
Sorry, Inspector Tsunemori!
すみません　先輩
I don't feel well, so please
excuse me. I'm heading back.
気分　悪いんで　先に帰らせてください
Huh?
That girl seems
quite scared of me.
あのお嬢ちゃん　よっぽど　俺が怖いらしい
すみません
I'm sorry.
The clearer one's Psycho-Pass is,
サイコパスがクリアな者ほど　他人に濁らされるのを恐れる
the more they're afraid
of having it clouded by others.
She must've thought that her Crime Coefficient
would go up by talking to me.
俺と話せば　犯罪係数が上がると思ったんだろ
If she had read my file,
that's just natural.
資料　読んだなら　無理もない
Is that so?
そういうものですかね
The odd one here is you.
You should realize that.
お前さんは　変わり者なんだぞ
もっと自覚を持て
But my Psycho-Pass never got clouded
by talking to you, Mr. Saiga.
でも　私は雑賀先生と話しても
サイコパス　濁ったことありませんから
Oh, that's right.
そうだったな
それで　俺に何の用だ？
So... what brought you here?
Please tell me...
Do I appear sane to you?
聞かせてください　私は正気に見えますか？
A message no one
could've written, huh?
誰にも書くことができないはずの　メッセージか
Right, except one person.
ええ　１人を除いて
True, if it's your own room,
確かに　自分の部屋になら
it's easy to write a message
without leaving any logs.
ログを残さず　メッセージを書くことは容易だな
I see...
なるほど
So you want to use me
as a mirror, huh?
俺を　鏡として使おうってわけか
For something like that,
you should ask someone healthier to help you.
そういうのは　もっと　健全な人間にやってもらえ
I'm not suited for the job.
俺には不適切な役割だな
I don't know anyone
better suited than you.
先生以上の人は知りませんから
Good grief...
やれやれ　じゃあ　まず　答えを聞かせろ
Well then, tell me
the answer first.
You figured out what
the message means, right?
分かったんだろ？　メッセージ
はい　彼の言葉を聞いて　ようやく確信しました
Yes. I'm finally convinced
after hearing what he said.
Hey, tell me...
what color am I now?
なあ　教えてくれよ…
俺は　今　何色なんだ？
"WC?" stands for "What color?".
「ＷＣ？」は　「What Color？」のイニシャル
「What Color？」「何色か？」
What color...?
That's a strange question
in this day and age.
このご時世に　妙なことを問うもんだ
Right. If the "color"
suggests Hue,
そうなんです　色というのが色相を指すなら
I don't see the point in asking
that question to humans.
わざわざ　人に問う意味が　分からない
You can easily check it
using a checker.
その程度は　チェッカーで　簡単に確認ができます
To start with,
who is this message for?
そもそも　こいつは誰に対するメッセージだろうな
Someone who was
at the crime scene,
現場にいた人物か
or the MWPSB people
who'd see it later, or...
それを見ることになる　公安の人間か　あるいは…
A question to themselves...
自分への問いか
One common thing between
these two messages is that
２つのメッセージに共通すること
それは　現場の監視官以外　書いた人物が　いるはずがないということ
no one else could've written it besides
the Inspector who was there at the site.
Inspector Aoyanagi said
it'd have to be a ghost.
青柳監視官は　それを指して　透明人間と言いました
自分の色を見失い　問うて回る　透明人間か
A ghost who lost sight of their color
and is asking around about it?
Sounds like a fairy tale.
おとぎ話だな
Could you tell me
what you think?
先生のお考えを　聞かせていただけますか？
A missing Inspector and messages
that can't possibly exist...
監視官の失踪　そして　あるはずのないメッセージ
I'm going to investigate this case,
私は　この件の捜査を　進めようと思っています
but I don't think
it'll be so easy.
だけど　一筋縄では　いきそうにない
だから　こんなロートルに頼ってきたわけか
That's why you came to see
this oldster to get help, huh?
I'm flattered.
うれしいね
You're the only one
who can help me.
先生しか　いないんです
Then, let's start with
the undeniable facts of the case...
まずは　変えようのない事象　確実に起こった事実を挙げてみろ
...the things we're
certain happened.
壁に書かれたメッセージ
The message written
on the walls...
...and Kitazawa's Crime Coefficient
decreasing that time.
そして　一度は下がった　喜汰沢の犯罪係数
Right. Next, let's identify the things
that are only a guess at this point.
そうだな
なら　逆に想像にすぎない事象は　何だと思う？
The existence of a person
who evaded scans and wrote the messages.
スキャンをかいくぐり　メッセージを書いた人物の存在
The existence of Kamui,
who supposedly lowered
喜汰沢の犯罪係数を下げたとされる　鹿矛囲という存在
Kitazawa's Crime Coefficient.
That's right. But even if
this Kamui guy doesn't exist,
そのとおり
しかし　その鹿矛囲ってやつが　存在しないとしても
the person who wrote
the message
メッセージを書いた人物と
喜汰沢の犯罪係数を下げた方法は　確かに存在する
and the means of lowering Kitazawa's
Crime Coefficient indeed exist.
This is what's called
the "Devil's Proof."
いわゆる　悪魔の証明ってやつだな
The Devil's Proof...
悪魔の証明…
現時点で　透明人間の存在を証明する方法はない
At this point, there isn't any way
to prove that this ghost exists,
but at the same time, we also aren't able
to disprove its existence, either.
だが　逆に　いないと断定することもできない
In other words,
I don't know what to do.
つまり　お手上げだよ
Then that means if we can prove
the existence of this ghost,
だったら　透明人間がいることを　証明できれば
there's a way forward, right?
まだ　手はあるってことですね？
Are you trying
to negotiate with me?
俺と交渉しているつもりか？
Inspector Shisui from Division 2
is considered to be acting solo
二係の酒々井監視官は独走扱いのまま
and is still missing.
いまだ　行方不明です
そのことに　先生なら思うことがあるんじゃないですか
Don't you have some
thoughts about that?
After all, you turned yourself in
out of guilt over helping Mr. Kogami out.
狡噛さんに手を貸した　自責の念から
自ら進んで　ここに　収容されている　あなたなら
情に訴えて　どうにかなる相手だと思うのかな　俺が
You think I'm the type that can be
swayed by appeals to the heart?
You know the value of trying to do
all one can despite overwhelming odds.
わずかな可能性でも　手を　尽くすことの価値を知っている
You're that kind of person.
先生は　そういう人です
You are an excellent student.
優秀な生徒だよ　お前さんは
It's thanks to your guidance.
ご指導のおかげです
Would you like some?
It's liquor that my dad left behind.
入れるか　親父の残した酒だ
Are you joking?
I'm an Inspector.
冗談のつもり？　私は監視官よ
And a human.
そして　人間だ
Are you okay?
大丈夫か
That sounds sarcastic.
How can I be okay?
嫌みね　大丈夫なわけないでしょ
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい
いや
That's all right.
If you work as an Inspector
for ten years,
監視官を１０年　勤め上げれば　厚生省のポストが待っている
a position at the Ministry
of Welfare lies waiting for you.
My life from then on
would have been secure.
そこからは　人生安泰のはずだった
But life isn't so simple.
だけど　うまくいかないものね
Are you being sarcastic?
嫌みか
What?
今の俺には　耳が痛い
That's kind of a sore
subject for me now.
でしょうね
I would guess so.
I wonder where I screwed up.
どこで　道　踏み外したんだろう
When I helped Division 1
to let Kogami escape?
一係に協力して　狡噛君逃がそうとしたとき…
Or, when I shot "him"?
あるいは彼を撃ったとき…
彼…　執行官の…
Him? You mean that Enforcer...
It wasn't your fault.
お前に責任はない
It's an Inspector's duty
to shoot a running Enforcer.
逃亡した執行官を撃つのは監視官の責務だ
There are times when one's duty
and one's feelings don't align,
気持ちと責務は交わらない
wouldn't you say?
そういうことも　あるんでしょ
I sometimes wonder...
ふと思うことがあるの
...if I put a lid on my feelings
the moment I killed him.
彼を殺した瞬間に
私の感情にふたみたいなのが　できちゃったんじゃないかって
Lid?
ふた…
When both my joy and sadness
reach a certain point,
喜びも悲しみも
一定量までいくと　そのふたに引っ掛かって　それ以上はあふれてこない
this lid makes sure
they don't come flowing out.
全力で何かを感じようとしても
Even when I try to feel
with everything I've got,
ふたの外側の自分が　どこか冷めた目で見てる
it seems like I'm looking on
from outside of this lid with cold eyes...
That's how I feel.
そんな感覚
But...
だけどね…
I feel that this lid starts to come off
when I'm holding a Dominator.
ドミネーターを　手にしている間だけは
そのふたが　外れかける気がするの
Because it starts to come off,
my rationality stops it.
外れそうになるから　それを理性が止める
That rationality is indeed
what makes me an Inspector.
その理性こそが　私を監視官たらしめている
That time... when I shot
Kitazawa, too, I almost enjoyed it.
あのとき…　喜汰沢を撃ったときも
気分が良くなりかけた
That's a bit dangerous, isn't it...?
ちょっとヤバいわよね
今の私には　この仕事しかない
All I've got now is this job.
I'll definitely cling to it.
しがみついてみせる
Thanks for the drink.
It was good.
ごちそうさま　おいしかったわ
I wish we'd have had
a drink together sooner.
もっと早く　一緒に飲めたら　よかったのにね
If I were my old self,
I wouldn't have had a drink.
昔の俺なら　酒など飲まなかったさ
Who's this?
誰？
Inspector Aoyanagi,
it's me, Shisui.
青柳監視官…
酒々井です
The investigations of the missing
Inspector Shisui from Division 2
失踪した　二係　酒々井監視官の捜索
and the messages you believe
were left by someone...
および　何者かが残したとされる　メッセージの調査
I see... so you want me to let
Division 1 take the lead on them.
なるほど　これを一係に優先的に行わせてほしいというわけか
Yes, and of course, we won't
neglect our usual operations.
はい　もちろん通常業務をおろそかにするつもりは　ありません
Okay, I'll allow it.
許可しよう
Thank you very much, Chief.
ありがとうございます　局長
Inspector Shimotsuki, you can go.
霜月監視官　下がりたまえ
You want just me to leave?
私だけですか
I want to talk
to Inspector Tsunemori alone.
常守監視官と２人で話がしたい
Understood.
Well then, excuse me.
分かりました　失礼します
So... what do you
think of this case?
さて　今回の件について君はどう考えている
I have a question.
質問があるわ
Does someone not recognized
by Sibyl really exist?
シビュラに認識されない人間は　存在するの
No such person can exist.
そんなものは存在し得ない
But with that question,
I now know your thoughts on this case.
しかし　今の問いで　君がどう考えているのかは理解した
Do you doubt my sanity?
私の正気を疑う？
That would be
the normal judgment.
そうするのが通常の判断だ
But at the same time,
it's also intriguing.
だが同時に興味深くもある
Can one lose their sanity
when their Psycho-Pass is so clear?
そこまでサイコパスがクリアな状態で　正気を失うことがあり得るのか
If you want to just sit back
and watch, be my guest.
勝手に観察者を気取ればいいわ
Well, hold on. I have a question
about the Division 1 personnel.
まあ　待ちたまえ
一係の人員について聞きたいことがある
Is the new Enforcer doing okay?
新入りの執行官　あれは　うまくやっているか
You mean Enforcer Togane
and Enforcer Hinakawa?
東金執行官と　雛河執行官のこと？
Right, Sakuya Togane.
そう　東金朔夜
I want you to report on him
to me as often as possible.
あれの様子はできれば逐一報告してほしい
Why?
なぜ
Although it's been erased
from the official documents,
公的な記録では抹消されているが
he showed the highest
Crime Coefficient on record.
あれは観測史上最高値の犯罪係数をたたき出した人物だ
He's a useful model case.
Be careful how you treat him.
有用なモデルケースだ
扱いにはじゅうぶん注意するように
I know this will put you
through quite a bit.
みんなには苦労を掛けると思う
But an Enforcer died,
an Inspector disappeared,
だけど　執行官が死に　監視官が失踪し
and we cannot even
locate one Dominator.
ドミネーターまで紛失した　この件を
I can hardly think that
it's okay to leave this case alone.
私はどうしても捨て置いていいとは思えない
Tell us what you
really think, Tsunemori.
本音を言え　常守
What you're concerned about
is the ghost, isn't it?
お前が気に掛かっているのは透明人間だろ
Make sure this doesn't
become personal.
あくまで業務の範囲内に収めろよ
I'm going to ask
Ms. Karanomori to help us, too.
唐之杜さんにも協力してもらうつもりです
Please give me your assistance.
補佐　お願いしますね
This is an elevated
Area Stress Level warning!
エリアストレス上昇警報　港区　台場…
Inside Daiba Tower Hotel
in Minato Ward,
I'll go.
Ms. Kunizuka, Hinakawa, come with me.
出動します　六合塚さん　雛河　同行を
a Psycho-Pass above the regulation value
has been detected.
- Okay.
- O-Okay.
了解
りょ…了解
Inspector on duty, please go straight
to the site with Enforcers immediately.
There's no way Kamui exists.
鹿矛囲なんて　いるはずがない
You can go ahead and chase after
a culprit that doesn't exist...
いもしない犯人を追い掛けていればいいじゃないですか
This is an elevated
Area Stress Level warning!
Inspector Tsunemori.
先輩は
Inside Daiba Tower Hotel
in Minato Ward,
a Psycho-Pass above the regulation value
has been detected.
Let us start on our
investigation, too.
私たちも始めましょう
I did keep my eyes
peeled and searched,
現場に不審な点は　なかったわよ
but nothing suspicious
was found at the crime scene.
それこそ目を皿にして探してたんですけどね
Suppose Kamui exists...
鹿矛囲がいたとして
He pretended to be a hostage
to lure out the MWPSB.
その人物は人質のふりをして公安をおびき寄せ
Then, he killed an Enforcer
and abducted an Inspector.
執行官を殺害し　監視官を誘拐した
Why on earth...?
What's his goal?
いったいなぜ　目的は
メッセージの意味は
What's the meaning of the message?
Why did he set his eyes on me?
どうして私に目を付けたの？
危険だな　のめり込み過ぎだ
It's dangerous...
You're getting too obsessed with this.
Inspector Tsunemori is fine.
常守監視官なら大丈夫
It would take more than this
to cloud her Hue.
この程度で色相が濁る人じゃない
Now is the time for us to put the lessons
we've learned to good use
われわれは　今こそ過去の反省を生かし
and carry out a new policy!
新しい政策を実行せねばならないのです
This is all to improve
citizens' lives!
全ては国民のよりよい暮らしのために
In order to do so, first...
そのためにも　まずは…
It was a wonderful speech.
素晴らしい演説でした
Representative Kotoku Masuda.
増田幸徳　代議士
公安です
We're from the MWPSB.
A deterioration in your Hue
has been detected.
あなたの色相の悪化が検知されました
It's been diagnosed that
you need emergency therapy.
緊急セラピーを要するものと診断します
Please come with us.
ご同行ください
Th-There must be some mistake!
な…　何かの間違いだ
Hinakawa, restrain him.
雛河　取り押さえなさい
This is the right way
to do things.
これが　正しい在り方なのに
What does the Chief see
in someone like her?
どうして　局長は　あんな人を…
So, Inspector Shisui is here?
ここに　酒々井監視官が？
Yeah, she told me herself.
ええ　彼女自身が　そう言っていた
You guys stay here.
You don't wanna make things worse.
あんたたちは　ここに　いなさい
仕事を増やしたくないでしょ
Understood.
了解
No! That won't work!
違う　それじゃ駄目だ
Medication can't save anyone.
It changes nothing!
薬じゃ何も救われない
変わらないんだそんなんじゃ
But...
しかし…
Everyone needs to open their eyes.
They can't just rely on medication...
みんなも気付くべきなんだ　薬なんかに頼っていては　駄目だって
...if they really
want to be saved.
本当に救われたいなら…
I have to save you guys.
私はね　君たちを　救わなければならない
やめなさい
Stop it!
Crime Coefficient is 23.
「犯罪係数　２３　執行対象ではありません」
Not a target for enforcement action.
Trigger will be locked.
「トリガーをロックします」
This isn't possible...
そんな…
何だ？
What the hell...?
This...
これ…
Did you find something?
どうかしたか
メッセージが残されていた現場に出動した爆弾解体ドローン
The Drones sent to defuse the bombs
at the site where the message was left...
One of them was found some distance
from the crime scene.
そのうち１体が現場から離れた場所で回収され
しかも　メンテナンスに　回されている
On top of that,
it was sent in for maintenance.
The documentation says
that it was missing a part.
資料には「部品の紛失」とあるわね
Looks like the impact absorber that
was installed in it had been removed.
内蔵されていた　インパクト　アブソーバー
いわゆる　衝撃吸収シートが　外されていたみたい
It's hard to think that
it just came off by itself.
そんなものが自然に外れるとは考えにくい
Could it be...
まさか…
先輩
Inspector Tsunemori...
Ms. Shimotsuki?
What's the matter?
霜月さん　どうしたの？
Kamui!
Call Kamui in here!
鹿矛囲だ　鹿矛囲を呼んでくれ
He can make me clear!
鹿矛囲なら　クリアにしてくれるんだ
I want to be a savior.
私はね　救世主になりたいんだ
I want to save everyone...
みんなを救いたい
Just like Kamui does.
鹿矛囲のように
All is calm, all is bright
All is calm All is bright
A whispering fallen angel
Sasayaku tenshi wa ochite
囁く天使は堕ちて
Gently devours you, body and soul
Yasashiku hamu wa anata no subete o
優しく食むわ　あなたの全てを
It's my guilty
You notice me
Kidzuku
気づく　目を見開いてる
With your eyes wide open,
Me o mihiraiteru
A faint blue as lifeless as concrete
Honoaoi konkuriito
仄青い混凝土
In a cold tone,
Tsumetaku watashi o
冷たく私を
Call my name and give me a kiss
And then hold me in the arms of the empty shell that is your body
Soshite dakishimete anata no inai sono karada de
そして抱きしめて
あなたのいないその体で
That soul that you've cast out
Hakidashita sono inochi wa
吐き出しその生命は
Has not yet completely vanished
Mada katachi o nokoshiteiru wa
まだ形を残しているわ　紅く
I glimpse a vivid red eternity
Akaku azayaka na eien ga miete
鮮やかな永遠が見えて
It starts singing right next to me
Tonari de sore wa utaidasu
隣でそれは歌いだすわ
What was I born for
ねえ　私を愛して
Come on, love me
Nee watashi o aishite
Because I won't let you go
Hanasanai kara
離さないから
Hello my name is
A world where humans' state of mind
and the tendency of their personalities can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls
are commonly called 'Psycho-Pass.'
This story is fiction.
The names of all individuals and organizations
that appear in the show are fictitious,
and have no relation to those in existence in the real world.